A Guide to the Henry G. Kunkel papers, Rockefeller University Faculty FA273
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Professional Activities, 1958-1983; 4
  - Lectures and Manuscripts, 4.4
    - Lecture: Presentation of Students (Carr - Tomasi) (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Lecture: Prizes/Awards (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - Lecture: Seminar on Biochemical Methods - "Zone Electrophoresis" - Advance Notes, 1960 February 24 (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - Lecture: Talks at RU to Foundations, etc., 1974-1976 (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - Lecture: Trantman Lecture, undated (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - Lecture: Unidentified Lectures, undated (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - Lecture: Untitled (Box 55, Folder 13)
    - Lecture: Unititied Lectures & Mss., 1962-1973 (Box 55, Folder 14)
    - Lecture: Zone Electrophoresis (Box 55, Folder 15)
    - Lectures, 1958 (Box 55, Folder 16)
    - Lecture, 1959 (Box 55, Folder 17)
    - Lecture, 1960 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Lecture, 1961 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Lecture, 1962 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Lecture: American Society for Clinical Investigation, 1962 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Lecture, 1964 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Lecture, 1965 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Lecture, 1967 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Lecture, 1967 (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Lecture, 1968 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Lecture, 1969 (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Lecture, 1970 (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - Lecture, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - Lecture, 1972 (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - Lecture, 1973 (Box 56, Folder 14)
    - Lecture, 1974 (Box 56, Folder 15)
    - Lecture, 1975 (Box 56, Folder 16)
    - Lecture, 1976 (Box 56, Folder 17)
    - Lecture, 1977 (Box 56, Folder 18)
    - Lecture, 1978 (Box 56, Folder 19)
    - Lecture, 1980 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Lecture: Israel, Cell Lines, 1980 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Lecture: Israel, Ia Talk, 1980 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Lecture: Israel, Memb. Iqs., 1980 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Lecture, 1981 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Lecture, 1982 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Lecture, 1983 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Manuscript: Acetylator Phenotype in Idiopathic Systemic Lupus Erythematosus - Marcus M. Reidenberg, et. al., undated (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Manuscript: Allosuppressor and Allohelper - T Cells in Acute and Chronic Graft-versus-Host Disease - Steven T. Pals, Helga G!eichmann, and Ernest Gleichmann, 1983 (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Manuscript: Antigens, undated (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Manuscript: Anti-Igs and Their Idiotypes: Are They Part of the Immune Network?, Kunkel et al., undated (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - Manuscript: Association Between Endogenously Activated T Cells and Immunoglobulin - Secreting B Cells in Patients with Active Systemic Lupus Erythematosus - Philip L. Cohen, David A. Litvin and John B. Winfield, undated (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - Manuscript: Autolog. MLC Reactions - Vande - Stouwe, et al. - JEM, 1977 (Box 57, Folder 13)
    - Manuscript: Ben -Ami Sela and Gerald M. Edelman, 1975-1977 (Box 57, Folder 14)
    - Manuscript: Characterization of Cloned eDNA Representing Rat Myelin Basic Protein; Absence of Expression in Brain of Shiverer Mutant Mice ? Arthur Roach, Kevin Boylan, et al., undated (Box 57, Folder 15)
    - Manuscript: Clinical Significance of Anti-Double-Stranded DNA Antibodies Detected by a Solid Phase Enzyme Immunoassay - Thomas E. Miller, Robert G. Lahita, et al., 1980 (Box 57, Folder 16)
    - Manuscript: A Community -Acquired Outbreak of Pneumocystis Carinii Pneumonia, Initial Manifestation of Cellular Immune Dysfunction - Henry Masur, Mary Ann Michelis, et al., undated (Box 57, Folder 17)
    - Manuscript: Complement Deficiency States - Vincent Agnello, 1977 (Box 57, Folder 18)
    - Manuscript: Contrasting Pttns. His. in Pts. with RA. - Gibofsky et al. - Arth. & Rheum., 1978 June (Box 57, Folder 19)
    - Manuscript: Cross Reacting Idiotypes in the Human System, 1983 (Box 57, Folder 20)
    - Manuscript: A cross reaction bet. etc. - Gottlieb, et al. - J. Immunol., 1977 (Box 57, Folder 21)
    - Manuscript: Dem. of ANAE Activity etc. - Knowles, et al.. - Cell. Immunol., 1977-1978 (Box 57, Folder 22)
    - Manuscript: The Differential Diagnosis of Hairy Cell Leukaemia with a Panel of Monoclonal Antibodies - B. Falini, R. Schwarting, et al., undated (Box 57, Folder 23)
    - Manuscript: Differentiation of B Lineage Cells from Liver of Neonatal Mice. Generation of Immunoglobulin Isotype Diversity In Vitro - Jane E. Calvert, Mary F. Kim, et al. - J. Immunol., 1983 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Manuscript: Dis. Assoc. Ia-like Hu. Alloan. - Gibofsky, Winchester, et al. ? JEM, 1978 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Manuscript: Diversity of y Globulins and Antibodies, undated (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Manuscript: Drawings, Prints, Galleys, Drafts of Figures for Mss. And Slides? "Genetic variants of yG4 globulin", 1970 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Manuscript: Effect of Reductive Lactosamination on the Hepatic Uptake of Bovine Pancreatic Ribonuclease A Dimer - Glynn Wilson, undated (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Manuscript: Enhancement by Irradiated T Cells of Human Plasma Cell Production, Dissection of Helper and Suppressor Functions In Vitro ? Frederick P. Siegal & Marta Siegal (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Manuscript: Expression and Function of Transplantation Antigens with Altered or Deleted Cytoplasmic Domains - Martha C. Zuniga, Bernard Malissen, et al., 1983 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - Manuscript: Expression of I-AK class II genes in mouse L cells after DNA?mediated gene transfer - Bernard Malissen, Michael Steinmetz, et al., 1983 (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Manuscript: Expression of la-like etc. - Winch., et al.. - PNAS, 1977 (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - Manuscript: Expression of a Major T-Cell Surface Protein, GP 150, on Malignant B-Cells in Early Stages of Maturation - Bernt Axelsson, Ulla Hellstrom, et al., undated (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - Manuscript: Ferrarini, Manlio, 1981-1982, undated (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - Manuscript: Finding the T -Cell Antigen Receptor, Past Attempts and Future Promise - Mitchell Kronenberg, Ellen Kraig, and Leroy Hood, undated (Box 58, Folder 12)
    - Manuscript: For Dr. Kunkel - Jean Pierre Bouvet, undated (Box 58, Folder 13)
    - Manuscript: Further Studies on the IgM receptors located on the surface of B cells - M. Ferrarini, Giovanna Viale & Elisabetta Cosulich, undated (Box 58, Folder 14)
    - Manuscript: GAT-Specific T and B Cells Do Not Transcribe Similar Heavy Chain Variable Region Gene Segments - Ellen Kraig, Mitchell Kronenberg, et al., undated (Box 58, Folder 15)
    - Manuscript: The Generation of Self Tolerance and of Antibody Diversity?Niels Kaj Jerne -, undated (Box 58, Folder 16)
    - Manuscript: Glomerular Localization of DNA and Antibodies to Nuclear Constituents, undated (Box 58, Folder 17)
    - Manuscript: H Chain Subgroups - Related Charts & Graphs, 1959-1964 (Box 58, Folder 18)
    - Manuscript: Hoffman -Lassiter cells, 1972, undated (Box 58, Folder 19)
    - Manuscript: Hoffman's Paper, 1981, undated (Box 58, Folder 20)
    - Manuscript: Human Anti-Idiotypic Antibodies, undated (Box 58, Folder 21)
    - Manuscript: The Human Ia System, undated (Box 58, Folder 22)
    - Manuscript: Hum. Lymp. bearing Ia etc. - Hoffman et al.. - J. of lmm., 1977 (Box 58, Folder 23)
    - Manuscript: Human malignant T cells capable of inducing an immunoglobulin class switch, undated (Box 58, Folder 23)
    - Manuscript: Hyper-IgM Immunodeficiency - Daniel Levitt, et al. - J. Clin. Invest, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Manuscript: Identification of a Particular B Cell Alloantigen Associated with Susceptibility to Lepromatous Leprosy - Me Patarroyo, et al - Dedicated to Dr. Henry Kunkel on his 65th birthday, undated (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Manuscript: Idiotypic Cross Reactions of Monoclonal Human Lupus Autoantibodies - Yehuda Shoenfeld, David A. Isenberg, et al., undated (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Manuscript: IgM Receptors on B Lymphocytes - Ferrarini, et al. - J. lmm., 1977 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Manuscript: Immunoglobulin heavy chain and serum prealbumin loci are distal on mouse chromosome 12 - submitted to Nature, undated (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Manuscript: The Immunologic Approach to SLE - H. Kunkel, 1976-1977 (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Manuscript: Immunological Studies Concerning the Nephritis of Systemic Lupus Erythematosus, undated (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Manuscript: Inhibition of Autologous Mixed Lymphocyte Response by Aggregated IgG Molecules - Dieter Kabelitz, et al., undated (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Manuscript: Inhib. of Human Erythropoietic Colony Form. - Winchester et al. ? JEM, undated (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - Manuscript: J. Donald Capra, undated (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - Manuscript: Kishimoto, Tadamitsu, et al - "Activation of Human Monoclonal B Cells with Anti-Ig and T Cell Derived Helper Factor (S) and Biochemical Analysis of the Transmembrane Signaling in B Cells", undated (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - Manuscript: Leroy Hood, 1977, 1981-1982 (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - Manuscript: Localization of Amyloid -Related Serum Protein SAA-like Material to Intermediate Filaments of Cultured Human Embroynal Fibroblasts - E. Lindar, J.B. Natvig, et al., 1977 (Box 59, Folder 13)
    - Manuscript: Mapping by Restriction Enzyme Site Polymorphisms - Astar Winoto, Michael Steinmetz, and Leroy Hood, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 14)
    - Manuscript: Measles Virus Proteins in the Brain Tissue of Patients with Subacute Sclerosing Panencephalitis - William W. Hall and Purnell W. Choppin, undated (Box 59, Folder 15)
    - Manuscript: Methods Enumerat. Lym. - Winchester & Ross - Clin. lmmun., 1976 (Box 59, Folder 16)
    - Manuscript: Miscellaneous Charts & Graphs, undated (Box 59, Folder 17)
    - Manuscript: Misc. Drawings, Charts & Photographs from Various Mss., 1980-1982, undated (Box 59, Folder 18)
    - Manuscript: Misc. Manuscript -Related Charts, Notes & Figures, undated (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Manuscript: Misc. Manuscripts, 1980, undated (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Manuscript: Misc. Manuscripts - Typed and handwritten, undated (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Manuscript: MLC Determinants in the North American (New York City) Caucasian Population as Defined by MLC Homozygous Test Cells, Proceedings of the 6th International Histocompatability Workshop Conference, 1975 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Manuscript: Molecular Characterization of the Recombination Region of Six Murine Major Histocompatability Complex (MHC) I Region Recombinants - Joan A. Kobori, Astar Winoto, et al., undated (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Manuscript: Mott Cells in a Patient with Lymphoproliferative Disorder - D.N. Posnett, et al., undated (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - Manuscript: Mt. Sinai, undated (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Manuscript: Mouse Spleen Lymphoblasts Generated In Vitro, Their Replication and Differentiation In Vitro - Ralph M. Steinmann, et al., undated (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Manuscript: Nucleotide Sequence of a Light Chain Gene of the Mouse I-A Subregion: AdB - Bernard Malissen, 1983 (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - Manuscript: Obituaries - Hereman & Franklin, 1975, 1982 (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - Manuscript: Oxytocic Activity of Purified Vasopressin - Draft & Notes, 1952 (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - Manuscript: Pancreatic Ribonuclease: Enzymic and Physiological Properties of a Cross -linked Dimer - Stanford Moore and Jacques Bartholeyns, 1974 (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - Manuscript: Parallel Syn., oflmm. etc. - Mestechy, Winch., Hofœ, Kunkel ? JEM, 1976 (Box 60, Folder 13)
    - Manuscript: Patterns of Expression ... - Halper et al. - J. Immunol. (sub.), 1977 (Box 60, Folder 14)
    - Manuscript: Peroxides & Fluorochrome Conj. Antisera etc. - Knowles, Winchester, Kunkel - C.I.I.. Clinical Immunology & Immunopathology, 1976-1977 (Box 60, Folder 15)
    - Manuscript: Phorbol Ester - Induced Enhancement of Immunoglobulin Gene Expression in Chronic Lymphocytic Leukemia - Jeffrey Cossman, Leonard M. Neckers, et al - Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences, undated (Box 60, Folder 16)
    - Manuscript: The Preparation of Mouse VH Fragments and the Characterization of Heterologous Anti-Mouse VH Antibodies - Klaus Karjalainen, undated (Box 60, Folder 17)
    - Manuscript: Purification of Biologically-Active Fey Receptor from Rabbit Alveolar Macrophanges - Anthony Kulczycki, Jr., Valerie Krause, et al., undated (Box 60, Folder 18)
    - Manuscript: RA-Urea-Hans, 1956-1958 (Box 60, Folder 19)
    - Manuscript: Reassessment of the Clinical Significance of Native Deoxyribonucleic Acid Antibodies in Systemic Lupus Erythematosus ? Michael F. Miniter, B. David Stollar, and Vincent Agnello, 1977 (Box 60, Folder 20)
    - Manuscript: Restriction of Human Immune Antibodies to Heavy Chain Variable Region Subgroups - O. Forre and J.B. Natvig, 1976 (Box 60, Folder 21)
    - Manuscript: Rheumatoid Factor Work -(drawer 5), 1960-1983 (Box 60, Folder 22)
    - Manuscript: R.H. Infantile Hypoimmunoglobulinemia without X-link Inherit.?T.H. et al - Clin. Immuno. & Immunopath., undated (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Manuscript: RNA Transcripts for I-J polypeptides are Apparently Not Encoded Between the I-A and I-E subregions of the Murine Major Histocompatability Complex - Mitchell Kronenberg, Michael Steinmetz, et al., 1983 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Manuscript: Serum and Cellular Ig. - Kunkel, H.G. - Clinical Chemistry, 1977 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Manuscript: A Simian Sarcoma Virus one Gene, v-sis, Is Derived from the Gene(s) Encoding a Platelet-Derived Growth Factor - Science, 1983 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Manuscript: Simultaneous Absence of the Human IgGI, IgG2, IgG4 and IgAl Subclasses: Immunological and Immunogenetical Considerations - Gerard Lefranc, Hassen Chaabani, et al., undated (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Manuscript: SLE Assoc. with Klinefelter's Syndrome - Stem, Fishman, etc.? "Arthritis and Rheumatism", 1976 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Manuscript: Structure and EVolution of Immunoglobulins, undated (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Manuscript: Studies on Syngeneic Mixed Lymphocyte Reaction III. Development of Monoclonal Antibody with Specificity for Autoreactive T Cells - Pierre B. Hausman, Charles E. Moody, et al., undated (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Manuscript: A Study of CSF Idiotypes in Multiple Sclerosis - G.C. Ebers, 1981 April (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - Manuscript: Subgroups and Gm System, 1961, 1964, undated (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - Manuscript: Systemic Lupus Erythematosus, undated (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - Manuscript: Three T-Cell Hybridomas Do Not Contain Detectable Heavy Chain Variable Gene Transcripts - Mitchell Kronenberg, Ellen Kraig, et al., undated (Box 61, Folder 12)
    - Manuscript: Untitled - Robert E. Cone, Richard K. Gershon, and Philip W. Askenase, undated (Box 61, Folder 13)
    - Manuscript: Techniques of Sur. Immunofluor. .. -Winchester - In Vitro Meth., 1976 (Box 61, Folder 14)
    - Manuscript: Transcript - SLE Symposium, 1982 (Box 61, Folder 15)
    - Manuscript: The Use of Univalent Antibodies to Kill Tumour Cells - M.J. Glennie and G.T. Stevenson, undated (Box 61, Folder 16)
    - Manuscript: Vasopressin, undated (Box 61, Folder 17)
  - Reviews, 4.5
    - Acta Pathologica et Microbiologica Scandinavica, 1975 (Box 61, Folder 18)
    - American Journal of Human Genetics, 1975 (Box 61, Folder 19)
    - American Journal of Medicine, 1971-1983, undated (Box 61, Folder 20)
    - The American Journal of Pathology, 1982 (Box 61, Folder 21)
    - Analytical Biochemistry, 1974, 1976 (Box 61, Folder 22)
    - Arthritis and Rheumatism, 1973-1982 (Box 61, Folder 23)
    - Biochemistry, 1973 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Blood, 1969-1982 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Cellular Immunology, 1976-1981 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Circulation, 1973 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Clinical Chemistry, 1973-1981 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - Clinical and Experimental Immunology, 1977 (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - Clinical Immunology and Immunopathology, 1973-1982 (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - Gastroenterology, 1981, 1983 (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - "Human Anti-Idiotypic Antibodies" - Review, undated (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - Human Lymphocyte Differentiation, 1980-1981 (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - International Journal of Immunochemistry, 1972-1973 (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - Israel Journal of Medical Sciences, 1975 (Box 62, Folder 12)
    - Johns Hopkins Medical Journal, 1976-1981 (Box 62, Folder 13)
    - Journal of the American Medical Association, 1974 (Box 62, Folder 14)
    - Journal of Cell Biology, 1974 (Box 62, Folder 15)
    - Journal of Clinical Investigation, 1971-1983 (Box 62, Folder 16)
    - Journal of Clinical and Laboratory Immunology, 1978 (Box 62, Folder 17)
    - Journal of Immunology, 1974-1979 (Box 62, Folder 18)
    - Journal of Laboratory and Clinical Medicine, 1973-1976 (Box 62, Folder 19)
    - Journal of Pediatrics, 1973-1976 (Box 62, Folder 20)
    - The Journal of Rheumatology, 1981 (Box 62, Folder 21)
    - lridney, 1974-1977 (Box 62, Folder 22)
    - "Koffler Review" (drawer 5), 1981 (Box 62, Folder 23)
    - Laboratory Investigation, 1977 (Box 62, Folder 24)
    - Medicine, 1975 (Box 62, Folder 25)
    - Misc. Reviews and Related Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 62, Folder 26)
    - Nature, 1977-1983 (Box 62, Folder 27)
    - Nephron (Box 62, Folder 28)
    - New England Journal of Medicine, 1975-1981 (Box 62, Folder 29)
    - The New York Medical Quarterly, 1980 (Box 62, Folder 30)
    - Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences, 1972-1979 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences, 1980-1983 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Reviews of others' manuscripts, 1979-1982 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Scandinavian Journal of Immunology, 1972-1979, undated (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Scandinavian Journal of Immunology, 1982-1983, undated (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Science, 1973-1975, undated (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Vox Sanguinis, 1973-1979 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Winfield Review, 1975, undated (Box 63, Folder 8)
- Rockefeller University, 1959-1987; 5
  Series 5 Rockefeller University is arranged in the following subseries: Sub-series 1: Correspondence. Sub-series 2: General. Sub-series 3: Personnel.
  - Correspondence, 5.1
    - Administrative Correspondence & Memos, 1975, 1980 (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - Administrative Correspondence & Memos, 1982-1983 (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - Cancer Program - Dr. Allfrey, 1971 (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - Case Files, 1959-1960 (Box 63, Folder 12)
    - Detlev W. Bronk, 1972 February 9 (Box 63, Folder 13)
    - Dr. Kreek File, 1967-1979 (Box 63, Folder 14)
    - Grant Correspondence, 1977, 1982-1983 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Harold Islon, 1979-1980 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Harold Islon, 1980 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Hector File (Markey), 1978-1982 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Hughes, 1980 February 18-19 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Lahita Promotion, 1983 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Markey, 1982-1983 (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - Present Appointments, 1981 (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - Rockefeller University Papers, 1975-1976 (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - Rodney Nichols, 1975, 1979 (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - Rodney W. Nichols, 1983 (Box 64, Folder 11)
    - Students, 1977 (Box 64, Folder 12)
    - Woodd-Cahusac, 1982 (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - General, 5.2
    - Administration-Faculty, 1981-1983 (Box 64, Folder 14)
    - AIDS - Grant, 1982 (Box 64, Folder 15)
    - AIDS - Grant, 1982 (Box 64, Folder 15A)
    - Allergy and Clinical Immunology Program (continuation grant), 1983 (Box 64, Folder 16)
    - Allergy and Clinical Immunology Program (continuation grant), 1983 (Box 64, Folder 16A)
    - Allergy and Immunology Seminars/Symposium, 1983 (Box 64, Folder 17)
    - Committee for Carl Nathan, 1982 (Box 64, Folder 18)
    - Convocation Program, 1982 June 2 (Box 64, Folder 19)
    - Cornell Residents/HGK Division, undated (Box 64, Folder 20)
    - Expenses, 1974-1984 (Box 64, Folder 21)
    - Grant Application - New York State Department of Health, AIDS Institute, 1983 (Box 64, Folder 22)
    - Grant Awards, 1977-1984 (Box 64, Folder 23)
    - Grant Records, 1980-1982 (Box 64, Folder 24)
    - Grant Records, 1980-1982 (Box 64, Folder 24A)
    - Grants, 1980 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Hospital Committee Review, 1975-1978 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Hospital Procedures - Dr. Henry G. Kunkel, 1972 July 1 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Howard Hughes Medical Institute, 1979-1983 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Howard Hughes Medical Institute, 1979-1983 (Box 65, Folder 4A)
    - Howard Hughes Medical Institute, 1979-1983 (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Howard Hughes Medical Institute - New Haven, 1981 Aug. 3, 1981, 1983 (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Howard Hughes Medical Institute - New Haven, 1981 Aug. 3, 1981, 1983 (Box 65, Folder 6A)
    - Hughes Board, 1983 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Irnrnunology Course - Antigens and Antibodies Tutorial, 1974-1979 (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - Irnrnunology Procedures & Notations, undated (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - Institutional Review Board, 1979, 1982-1983 (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - Institutional Review Board Research Protocol Submission Procedure, 1982 (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - Memorandum - List of Students for Immunology Tutorial on Antigens and Antibodies, 1975 October (Box 65, Folder 12)
    - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center - Ad. Hoc Committee on Appointments and Promotions, 1982 (Box 65, Folder 13)
    - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center - Ad Hoc Committee on Appointments and Promotions, 1982 (Box 65, Folder 14)
    - Mink Disease - Research Grant, 1967 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Mink Disease - Research Grant, 1967 (Box 66, Folder 1A)
    - Misc. Correspondence & Reports, 1976-1983 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Patients - Doctors & Comments (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Philip Levine Lecture, 1976, 1979-1983 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - PHS AI 10811 Grant Renewal, 1971, 1978-1982 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Program - Rockefeller University Convocation for Conferring Degrees - annotation, 1981 June 11 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Proposal on Response to RFA NIH-NCI-DCT CTEP-82-13, 1982 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Proposal on Response to RFA NIH-NCI-DCT CTEP-82-13, 1982 (Box 66, Folder 7A)
    - Proposal on Response to RFA NIH-NCI-DCT CTEP-82-13, 1982 (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - Proposal on Response to RFA NIH-NCI-DCT CTEP-82-13, 1982 (Box 66, Folder 8A)
    - Proposal for Support of Research & Training in Environmental Sciences and Reproductive Biology, 1970-1971 (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - Renewal Application, RR-00102 - Volume 1 (missing pages), 1976 June 1 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - A Report to the Imperial Governrnent oflran on the Feasibility of Establishing a New Biomedical Research Institute, 1975 September 2 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Rheumatology, 1968-1982 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller University Hospital-Advisory Committee, 1979 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - RU Hospital Printout, 1980 December-1981 November (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - RU Hospital Seminars, 1980-1982 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - RU Memo - Equipment Costing, 1980 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Rockefeller University Senate, 1980, 1983 (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - Search Committee - Dr. Brunner, 1980-1983 (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - Thorn Committee, 1981-1983 (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - University Senate, 1976 (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - Personnel, 5.3
    - Adams, Linda, 1972-1975 (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - Agnello, Vincent, 1966-1978 (Box 67, Folder 13)
    - Agnello, Vincent, 1977 (Box 67, Folder 14)
    - Allen, James, 1961-1983 (Box 67, Folder 15)
    - Ambinder, Jeffrey M., 1976-1981 (Box 67, Folder 16)
    - Dr. Arena, 1977 (Box 67, Folder 17)
    - Bearn, Alexander G., 1959-1979 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Bentwich, Zvi, 1970-1981 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Berkower, Ira, 1976-1982 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Bhardwaj, Nina, 1983 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Bigler, Robert D., 1978-1986 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Biro, Carlos, 1959-1967 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Bouvet, Jean -Pierre, 1979-1980 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Brinkmann, Dennis J., 1974-1980 (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Brusman, Harold, 1970-1980 (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Burakoff, Steven, 1972 (Box 68, Folder 10)